From the shadows of the subconscious to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche
Awakens.
Crowd whoosh!
Sparkly chimes.
Thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness.
Buckle in tight.
Tarot on deck.
Third eye in flight.
True Skip told he goes unfold.
We stir the soul with a tea surf cold.
Panels be popping.
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stoppin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marbles fan from above
It's like the Awakens step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like the Awakens, don't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Okay, can we get ghosts up here?
Doctor, I just wanna make sure I get ghosts.
I see where he did donate again.
A sizable amount.
And so we'll see if anything goes up here.
Just.
To respect that that donation. I think I will be able to get my computer. Hey, Arbiter. Hey, he goes, okay
Okay, there you go that goes so goes tell me what you want with that. So he goes exactly what you want
Is that what you said there?
Because we have to agree with everybody
So I'm sorry if like he says someone's someone's kicked off for the day 24 hours or buddies
But you know, you know, it was my changes mind how he is. I just want to talk to him real quick goes D
There's oh, yeah, there's a link right here. Come on up
Once okay, here's goes once again goes are you so are you sure?
Did you or did you not kick summer?
Yes, yeah, we paid for that Christine. Would you like to pay for it not feel like that?
No, because we can't do reduce or we can't do that. Here's my next question site
He paid a hundred dollars. You know, you know what? I'll leave she can have tonight and this tomorrow will be my panel
Is that fine with you Christine? So you're gonna crash on it's not your panel. It's Sykes shut up for a moment
Well, I paid for it. I paid a lot more than
Here's my question. Yes. Yes. Here's my question. You guys can have it. How do you get to pay and then
Just kick one person but gonna save the rest for later. It doesn't work that way
I mean more money Christian you've heard of it. I I can't I mean it's like I'll give him credits for a future kick
I mean that's we're doing credits now. Stop. I mean
He paid it. He paid it and so I think I'll something I paid I paid a hundred dollars
Oh, thank you
You in you in summer change the roof. I'm crashing out you and summer can have this panel. I'm fine with that
You don't get over it over people's head psych he doesn't get to
You have your seven days to use
Okay, and you know if people feel like
You know
We don't change rule psych because you're money hungry right now
So the other night when he donated what he said 300 so now he can have six kicks
I'm not changing the rules. I'm not changing the rules, Kristian. I'm not changing the rules. I'm really giving her love for you, Kristian.
You don't have to give it up, I'm not staying.
You can have the panel.
I'm not.
I'm not paying for you, Christine.
Okay.
Goffin, why are you talking?
What do we like to do?
So it's always right?
I'll literally pay for you to be up here.
I can bring Summer up.
Go.
I can bring Summer up right now, correct?
I don't want Summer up here.
I want Christine.
Okay.
She's not talking.
You talk to Christine for a second.
I'll be right back.
I will literally pay for her to be up here.
No, I don't need you to pay for me to be up here.
Then why are you bitching? Why are you running that fucking mouth? Because I can
So you kick me
That's a good reason. I mean there you go. I thought you actually that's a good reason. Okay, cool. I don't need reasons
I'm a fucking grown-ass. Okay, then why are you even talking to me?
I also can't for you. It's I'm a fucking grown-ass woman. I could do as I damn well, please
Yeah, well, I'm done. I'm done talking to you ma'am. Oh
You're kicking me too and I paid
I paid a lot more money. Are you kicking me? It's a simple yes or no. No. Okay. Then I will run my mouth.
About what? Anything I choose. Anything I choose. Maybe you should learn how to pay more money.
Or shut the fuck up. You ever hear the argument? I paid some money tonight to have somebody kick you paid some way
I can see shit. It's like you see how much cash app and by the way, it's like you can't hurt the meme
Well, how much?
none of your business
My money like my business. I don't have to do that. I'm asking you a question. What you pay to announce it
Okay
You know see how much money I paid for tonight, I'm giving Christine immunity
Because she she just fuck that
No, I paid
A little bit of more than 25
Christine what I paid
Now she's gone and I paid no more than 25 right here
You can't you have to use it on somebody else. There you go. There's that
There's that
for seeing gets immunity
Anybody anybody that donates anybody that donates, you know to have someone kick that day gets immunity that day and I kicked already tonight
Yeah, yes
So there's that box. I paid $400 don't matter
Yeah, and I pay by what the rules say
Yes
So
Well at this point then I am it's fucking channel for like the next year and a half then
I won't say another word, but how much money to have I think God
You think it's quite quite a bit and it's like, you know, it's gonna be
No, it's not 2,000, but it's it's you're very nice for another one
It's a very nice
I appreciate you, but yeah, I'm offering. I'm gonna give pristine immunity because she did
You know do a kick today and so that'll be my new rule for the future is like if you do a kick that day
You're you're not gonna get kicked that day. No, we have to kick him before he gets on is what you're saying
Well, um, yeah, you'd have to be, yeah, I guess it'll be, yeah.
Um, so it kicks him plus gives us immunity. Gotcha.
For that day, for that, um, well, it's like, yeah, but it's 24 hours.
I'm good with it. You know, it's like I don't mind the rules and and I play by the rules
But one of the rules always change I have a problem. Well, we are it is the beginning stages where some single works out
It's kind of experimenting, you know, so like there's something doesn't quite work. I have to tweak it a little bit
I want to make sure you know
Everyone's happy, you know, it's hard to do
So if somebody kicks somebody and then they change their mind they can bring the person back is that a rule to them
I mean, let's get this all straight
But no refunds no refunds, but they can change their minds. They can change them as they okay bring them back
If that person says it's okay, then yes, okay
Can decide yes, okay
I just want to make sure that if somebody kicks but they choose to bring that person back they can't
Mm-hmm. Okay. No, I'm gonna I'm gonna tell you something because when that starts happening and people are brought back and kicked brought back and kicked
They're gonna leave your channel. I'm just letting you know this so think hard about it. Okay, yeah
Possibly, but it's like, you know, I do hope that people understand that this is like, you know, it's not like a lifetime ban
It's like it's just like a you know one day
which is like, you know, who knows? I understand. It helps the show and this is my monetization of the open panel so I can do more open panels or do more paneling and stuff.
No, I get it. I have no problem. You know, I have no problem with channel owners that charge to kick. I have none whatsoever.
It's just, you gotta maybe do the rules but not do it while it's happening.
Right, okay. Yeah, I know but sometimes you have to think on your feet and sometimes there's new situations that come up
And I just have to you know address them as they come and that's all I can do
It's like, you know, I
Like to play, you know, I knew I couldn't kick go so I chose to kick somebody else and it gives me immunity
I knew that
Yes, and so that's why I did it because he can't kick me
And as you want to thank you too, Christine, for that.
You're welcome.
Yes, thank you very much.
And not that I'm going to stay on long.
I really wasn't in the mood to come on panel.
I have a lot of things going on in my mind
that I've got to figure out.
And I have millions of papers in front of me,
so I've been a little busy.
No random guy.
You can't kick me.
I've already kicked somebody.
It gives me immunity.
I'm sorry. Um, hot mess, summer wants to know summer. It seems to be 24 hours unless
ghost chooses to bring you back. Just saying that's what the rule is.
Ghost, uh, ghost, you know, you can decide to do that. And so if you'd like, um, someone
back says, let me know as soon as possible.
Random. I didn't make the rule. You don't get your money back. You don't get money back.
Sorry, not sorry. Yeah, he has said that long ago. No refunds got that figured out
Sorry, sorry because I'm not going anywhere tonight
suck my dick
So goes to which like to do it tonight or another night or turn like tomorrow or how would you like to handle this?
How are you feeling tonight?
Let's see you go see
I don't know. Oh, he's gone. Okay. Oh goodness gracious. Hold on. How much now? Okay. Yeah
I don't know but why are you sending more money? I think we could go first of all. I can't refund the super chat
I don't have the ability to do it. You try to get me
Yeah, you can't you can't keep Christine go. I know he's not understanding that. Yeah, but if you look right underneath
This is by Christie
Christina's Christina's Christina's good today goes because she she paid for a kick
and so she's immune. I paid her kick. Sorry. Try tomorrow but maybe I'll get to you first.
That'd be fun.
Oh, she's a dweeb.
I wish I had that picture.
There is.
It's serious right here.
Summer, can you put the picture in messenger
so I can get a copy of this picture and put it up here?
I think I deleted it.
And I'll show you all who Ghost is.
He looks like you don't know you don't you know the top of the factory. You don't make me by the way second of all
I don't give a fuck what I look at that. How how's that doing?
Factory one of their if you're saying like we have to pay to kick the ball off and I gave you I guess so much money
Yeah, how many people do I get? Yeah, but at that time I didn't know Christine had donated tonight
I'm saying how many people
How many people I mean, so you said that you wanted you said you're 25
He said he said one you gave summer and they said you wanted the rest for later. Okay, so that's what that's where we are right now
But you have how long what would I get somewhere that you're just like I couldn't give her that
Because we just donated for a kick
I didn't and so what do you mean if you just don't I donated before that no it was a while ago
No, it was a while ago. He just didn't look
It was tonight. Was it not tonight though? Oh, yeah, it was tonight
Yeah, I donated how much before it doesn't matter. I did it before you start when that shit
Does matter yeah, he has arguments
Yeah, what's those 25 blue listen, man real quick the 25 to kick someone and I fucking donate 200 bucks
I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that. I got that
before
We even went I could give a million dollars. It wouldn't matter. It wouldn't matter at all. No
Well, you can get a million dollars and I may leave on my own
Well, if it's the million dollars, but the million dollars
Your father
You don't the fuck you're talking about do you know what a random man divided by
Random guy don't approach me like that. You know, that's a disrespect. Well, don't approach me like that
Okay, no, yeah, he called me a fucking retard. So it's like you don't have to say
Sir, I don't know what the fuck you are. I know that you
Like that
John, we can't kick ghosts tonight. We have to wait till tomorrow.
And you're sucking her dick instead of I how much money have I given you?
And how much money do you have? Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Check the score, your. No, let me.
Check the score. Check the score.
It's two thousand and one.
it doesn't matter
That's your husband. You're gonna end up here on yourself with that side that you shouldn't be
How much I gave oh my god, I can't even believe how much when I gave this
You should be gone. You should have been gone. I don't kick you don't fuck
I even gave no fuck that. Hey psyche. Did I not give you fit?
75 I think it was fifty seventy five dollars. I said kick this person. I said give me give me
I think it was 75 so because I said kick one person
Give me the next two
Before we started
Before the new
I mean, I'm giving Christine immunity. I get to I get to do one saved at least one safe
Because you donate it and I'll give you the same thing I'll give you the same thing
I would do not give that if you wouldn't have kicked somebody I would have kicked your ass by now
Well, how does she wait psyche real quick though because that's about point she get to kick somebody before me
At the last panel before he ended
I did it before you, and I've donated more money than you.
How do I not get that?
I'm not just kidding.
It doesn't matter how much I beat you.
Donate it.
But I did it before you on the left.
But I did it before you on the left, boy.
Sike, I did it before her and the last one you you you know that but you didn't
You said it was you said it was like a no date you did say it was a day
You said you should do whatever you want with this memory
Yes, and so
Change the thing and say oh well, I've given you all this money
I'm gonna kick for the next six months the way I want to so you just give money invisible
You don't know where the fuck it's going to you went to cash out
because you purposely joined this fucking one went to cash app. Yes.
And I did.
Hey, listen, I'm going to school everybody.
Hey, Saki, let me give me like give me like literally 10 seconds.
Let me school everybody.
That was the last panel.
But not this panel. I don't need a lot of money for this panel. It's for 24 hours. It doesn't matter. I literally donated seventy-four dollars just to kick people. It was for twenty-four hours.
And I kicked one person. You can't kick me. And you guys told me, Psyche told me to have two more people. That's right. That's right. And he told you, I kicked somebody which gives me immunity.
I didn't pay for you. I don't give a fuck. You kicked. I didn't pay for that. That's my money. I didn't pay for you. Sorry. I kicked somebody. It gives me immunity. What do you mean sorry?
What do you mean sorry I paid
So what we're gonna pay money for
I don't get it. What did I pay money for then? I don't know
And sake you're gonna gear with that
I'm letting you basically run the panel as you please, I said there's one person that
I'm not going to kick because she just donated and so, you know, I'm giving Christina immunity
tonight.
I paid to kick someone.
You can still kick anybody else off.
You know what?
Summer's not here.
No, it was about to leave and then use but and you keep like you're engaging her
Yeah, so
You want to talk shit a lot because I know you like to talk shit you want fuck you don't know much money
Somebody kicks it gives the person how much I paid shut the fuck up
Over two hundred dollars psyche guess what you gave me you give me shit. I paid over to her. No, I know
He goes goes
Exactly what you asked me to do exactly that's like
I brought back summer you said skin summer for five minutes with some other kicks
And then I were in them that I did and then you're like, okay now kick her up for a day
And then it's like you change your mind you have to specify and so I'll keep that
I'll give you the other three
three cases to do
If you were if you were if you were around me
I'd punch you in the fucking mouth honestly after that bullshit. Wow. All that money I gave you really all that money I gave you really
I'll make it I'll make it for you
Go see those
Little threatening are we?
The channel owner discussing man, they don't know that was disgusting behavior
threatening a channel owner should automatically get you removed
It doesn't matter what you pay.
Oh, for what?
You're gonna take my money, disrespect me,
and then kick me out?
I'm not trying to disrespect you, ghost.
You're threatening him.
I ain't threatening nothing.
How am I threatening? Go ahead and explain it.
Bitch, I'm gonna burn you up.
Adam, you're in the physical violence.
I said if you were a nigga, I'd punch you in your fucking mouth.
How am I threatening you? You're not a nigga.
He needs to go to back for a while.
Ghost now. I ain't going nowhere. I gave no he needs to go to back for a while. That's inappropriate. I ain't going nowhere
You're not gonna influence them that is
Racial slur what the fuck is wrong with you? Ghost never once made up. What's the racial slur? Go ahead and explain it to me
Look at this. Look at this guys. Look. Look there. I am look
Wow, you think it's not real. It is real see
Beautiful
Yeah, you look like you look like Alec Goldman
That's kind of funny. I kind of like how I mean I fall in the bar at like all drunk
Okay, hold on this way you weren't you look like you're wearing the same shirt, buddy. I
Kind of night. No, it wasn't tonight, but how do I get out of this? Okay save it. Okay
Okay there and I can do another one too. Oh here. I'm doing stand up. I'll give you one more deal one more deal before
I go to bed if okay, let's go. Let's go
The rental I'll give another 20. That's fair dude. I'll give another fucking 20 bucks if the wrenches will join
Okay, rent fair
Is this summer included or she's still up?
No, no, I'm not somewhere out. I'll talk to her tomorrow. I'm sure we'll okay. Yeah, we'll talk tomorrow
Okay, so if that's fine with you brother, it's your
You know, you think so I'm gonna I think I'm gonna you know last 20 bucks the last 20 wrenches, you know
Okay, well, so let's see what we have this cheese. He's in this guy's gonna just yell at me though here
Who is it listen to me psych are you listening?
No, yes
All right
I've sent you like 300 bucks the last month. That's more that's more than a Netflix subscribe
Do you think you're worth more than Netflix? That's very much
That's very much more
That's more than Netflix
It's like a Lisa Dordotta like you're taking abuse from
You had her back
Yeah, you know you're doing that stupid
Stupid the fuck is you like to play stupid, but you're not stupid. Do you like to play it?
That's down a comedy machine. This is what we got
I'm trying to help
I love you here. Hold on a second. Well, no fuck all that shit Brian gonna guy gave you more money than anybody up at this motherfucker
name
You're up here with me goes I love you you're up here with me. Okay, so you're up here nobody
I paid to be up here. You know I paid to be up here
I love you and you're here look. I'm honoring. Well. No, you don't love me at all. You're fucking
Fake crime, we don't give a fuck we don't care, you know, you did
Don't be mad goes
New money
I thought you were a little too long. Okay. Okay. Well, okay. I'll just say I'm gonna I'll see you. I'll see you at
9 30 or 10 p.m. What do you prefer it's gonna be either
No, I'll be back. Oh, I'm gonna I'm gonna be back at either 930
I mean if you run me I beat the brakes up. You're like what hey
930 or 10 o'clock just tell me tell me when you want me back
Also, I'll start to show you a 930 or 10 o'clock. Tell me what time you're gonna start the show
Let me join and then you just yeah
No, no, I'm gonna I'm gonna restart the show and let you and then you run it
But I'm gonna just start that shit. We're all you when you restart that shit then we get nobody up here
Okay, well, if anyone wants to come you're welcome. It's but I'm you know, I'm not gonna be yelled at and like
No, just respect it. It's like I'm trying to make everyone happy. I'm you know, you gotta give me a break
It's well, sir. Did you feel disrespected? Let me take time out of my day
Do apologize. I didn't mean to disrespect you, but I
Disrespected and as your friend I felt disrespected. It's hard to get that
Look at that. Look at this. So it's it's it's it's hard being you but it's not hard being your friend
Like I can't though be my friend. Look at look at look at look at cool. This is I put on glasses
Pretty good watch over though. It's kind of hard being your friend, brother
I'm sorry. I know maybe it maybe it is. Maybe I'm just a music
You don't have to have everyone said apologize to you ever once a day in our relationship
No, never said that you don't have to
I hope I'm sorry. I'll make it. I'll try to be better friends
I'm not perfect here. Look at my aliens. See he's holding the cat. He's like, you know
So if you're my little brother, I would you know, I would do
But in your wedgie, I would love you and take care of you, but you know what? I wish I could do
What has to be in the mouth?
Some hands on you. Yeah
Okay, well, you know, that's what brothers can sometimes do that too
I grew up with actually brothers my brothers are like 10 years and 12 years older than me
And so I it was you know, I was beat up
Yes, they're football players football baseball players. They were the jocks you know
I wasn't know I was like a little delicate, you know little little I think to read books and they know
You know, it's a quietly, but I have my brother's
My birthday it's coming up. Oh
Good, so your birthday. Um, so you're Leo, right?
Sorry
Okay, we'll have you know happy birthday, I'm gonna you know, I mean I'm gonna I'm gonna jump out of a cake for you
You like that you're gonna jump out of what sorry go ahead brother a cake a cake on your birthday
Whoa nice brother
Yes, I will you're gonna cook it yourself. You're it
I'll try I'll try see if anything I'll build it. I'll make a small cake and I'll just I'll sit sit on it
Listen sir, I think after all this money I gave and I knew you're gonna go to bed
Is there any way any possible way to bed because you're not gonna give me permission, but I don't know if anybody's gonna stay up
Is there any way we can keep it open at all for the rest of the people?
Yeah, I'll I'll stay here. I'll stay here and do it like I was just like I just can't like have like
You know I'm talking about hoping for me like you can open up for everyone
Yes, you can I have to be able to kick I have to be able to kick though because you know pieces of shirt
Okay, so you'd like to like to like say, you know, okay now I'd like to bring this person on and this person off
Thank you, right? That's what you'd like to say. He'd like to just be I never once I want to bring any of them on
I'm saying brand of people if they want to join they should be able to I should be able to yes
Let's open I have to have the I have to be able to kick off because what if they are pieces of shit?
No, I'll be here
I'll be here. I'll be I'll sit right here. I'll be listening. Well, fuck it. Let's run the last
How late you're gonna stay up ten minutes twenty minutes
Well, I was gonna like to take a little break and then come back and then step into like two or three like ten to two
Or ten to three like in it like four or five hours
Okay
We'll do ten tell us that will attend
You have a question so we lost goes it sounds like but
It sounds like we're back at 10 p.m. Pacific tonight. It's just an hour and ten minutes or hour nine minutes, okay?
Me the control where you going? We got to be able to control
I was gonna say can we take a break and then start at 10 10 to two or 10 to three
We'll all run and I'll just we'll just do a little hour break right now. Yeah, I kind of want to run it with them
I kind of want it. It's like you real quick. I kind of want the Mars to join for the
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna write I'm gonna write in my discord with all my mother my discord
I'll write a message in my discord to come to the show, okay, and we'll see I hopefully hopefully everyone will come
Well, well, yeah, we'll have it open free for all. Okay. I love you guys. I'll be back at 10 o'clock. I'll see you a little bit